Learning how to communicate insight from
يُعد تعلم كيفية توصيل الرؤى من البيانات
data is one of the most crucial skills anyone can have.
واحدة من أهم المهارات التي يمكن أن يمتلكها أي شخص.
And usually, the most compelling way to communicate information about data is visually,
وعادة، ما تكون الطريقة البصرية هي أكتر الطرق اقناعًا لتوصيل معلومات عن البيانات.
but creating good data visualizations really combines two skills.
ولكن إنشاء عروض جيدة للبيانات يجمع بين مهارتين.
First, there is a design and artistic component to
أولًا، التصميم والمحتوى الفني
create something that is beautiful and compelling.
لصنع شيء جميل ومقنع.
And then, there's a strong scientific and mathematical component
ومن ثم، يأتي المكون العلمي والرياضي
in being able to deliver the right insights.
القوي في قدرته على توصيل الرؤى الصحيحة.
The role of the next lessons is to help you build
ويتمثل دور الدروس القادمة في مساعدتكم على إنشاء
data visualizations and do so in a way that is engaging and informative.
مرئيات البيانات والقيام بذلك بطريقة جذابة وغنية بالمعلومات.
Specifically, in this lesson you will learn why
وبشكل خاص، ستتعلمون في هذا الدرس لماذا
data visualizations are more useful than just
تعتبر عروض البيانات أكثر فائدة من مجرد
using some real statistics and you will learn
استخدام الإحصاءات الحقيقية وستتعلمون أيضًا
the most common plots used in data visualization.
الرسوم الأكثر شيوعًا المستخدمة في عرض البيانات.
We will finish the lesson by introducing
سننهي هذا الدرس بتقديم
a data dashboard in motivating the next lesson on design principles.
لوحة معلومات البيانات للتحفيز للدرس القادم عن مبادئ التصميم.